expertsacademy.com 2008-12-18

# LIFE'S GOLDEN TICKET BY BRENDON BURCHARD - OFFICIAL SITE

** PRIVACY POLICY**

** We are committed to protecting the privacy and security of the users of our sites.**

This privacy policy will advise you about how we use and protect your personal information, and about what choices you have concerning our use of such information. If you have objections to the Privacy Policy, you should not access or use any of the pages of [ www.LifesGoldenTicket.com](http://www.collegesuccessbootcamp.com/). (Collectively referred to from now on as the Site). We encourage users to regularly review our Privacy Policy as we may need to change the policy from time to time. We will post those changes on the Site, accessible through the homepage, so that you will always know what information we gather, how we might use that information, and whether we will disclose that information to anyone. 

** About this website and collectors of information**  
www.LifesGoldenTicket.com is the website of  The Burchard Group LLC. This website is operated, controlled and maintained by The Burchard Group LLC (referred to from here forward as “We”.) 

Our postal address is:  
 The Burchard Group LLC  
2269 Chestnut Street #172  
San Francisco, CA 94123.  

We can be reached via email at info@LifesGoldenTicket.com or by telephone at 1-800-816-8528. 

The Site contains links to other websites, like our sponsor’s websites or links to booksellers, that may offer products or services that our customers might find useful. These sites may request information from you. In such instances, the collection and use of your personal information will be governed by the privacy policy applicable to that site. We do not control the privacy policies, contents or links that appear on these sites. We encourage you to review the privacy policies of any third party sites or services before providing any of them with your personal information. 

** How and why we collect information**

We collect your information in order to record and support your participation in the activities you select. If you register for a seminar, for example, the information is used to reserve your seat, to track your preferences, and to keep you informed about the seminar and related events. 

As a visitor to the Site, you can engage in many activities without providing any personal information. In connection with other activities, such as utilizing registering for a seminar or participating in a sweepstakes, we may ask you to provide certain information about yourself by filling out and submitting an online form. It is completely optional for you to engage in these activities. If you elect to engage in these activities, however, we may ask that you provide us personal information, such as your first and last name, mailing address (including ZIP code), e-mail address, , telephone, credit card, and other personal information. If you do not provide the mandatory data with respect to a particular activity, you will not be able to engage in that activity. In all cases, we will collect personal identification information from you only if you voluntarily submit such information to us. We will also tell you how we use your information or if we share it with another party. Except as otherwise provided in this policy, we will never intentionally disclose any personal identification information about you as an individual user to any third party without having received your permission. 

If you supply us with your contact information you may receive periodic e-mails, mailings or calls from us with information on new products and services, important issues, or upcoming events. If you wish to be removed from any postal, email, phone, or other lists, please let us know by emailing us at unsubscribe@LifesGoldenTicket.com. You can also write us or call us at the contact information above. Please provide us with your exact name, email address, mailing address, and phone. We will be sure your name is removed from the appropriate lists immediately. 

When you use the Site, we or our authorized technology services provider may also collect certain technical and routing information from you to facilitate your use of the Site and its services. We use this information to administer the Site and to understand and measure traffic patterns on the Site so that we know which areas of our sites are favorites of our users, which areas need improvement, and what technologies are being used so that we may continually improve our sites. This information is collected in aggregate form, without identifying you or any user individually. We may use this aggregate, non-identifying statistical data for statistical analysis, marketing, or similar promotional purposes. This data is often tracked by us our our technology services provider by using "cookies" during your visit. A cookie is small amount of data that is transferred to your browser by a web server and can only be read by the server that gave it to you. It functions as your identification card and enables us to record your passwords, purchases, and preferences. It cannot be executed as code or deliver viruses. Most browsers are initially set to accept cookies. You can set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie, giving you the chance to decide whether or not to accept it. (For some web pages that require an authorization, cookies are not optional. Users choosing not to accept cookies will probably not be able to access those pages.)

** Exceptions to policy**

While we are committed to keeping your information secure and private, we have the following exceptions to our privacy policy: We will release specific information about you or your account to comply with any valid legal inquiry or process such as a search warrant, subpoena, statute or court order. We will also release specific information in special cases, such as if there is an attempted breach of the security of the Sites, or a physical or property threat to you or others. We may also transfer user information, including personally identifiable information, in connection with a corporate merger, consolidation, the sale of related assets or corporate division or other fundamental corporate change. 

Further, the information you enter when making a purchase or an online donation will be shared with payment processors, financial gateways, and your credit card company to authorize credit card payments. Such information may also be shared with necessary third parties solely for the purpose or carrying out the transactions. 

Please note that if you give out personal information online through a discussion board or posting site, that information can be collected and used by third parties. Although we strive to protect our users' privacy, we cannot guarantee the security of information you post in these forums. You disclose such information at your own risk. 

** Submissions policy**

You acknowledge and agree to the following terms and conditions when submitting any ideas, secrets, suggestions, materials, videos, photographs, etc. to us by email or through our website entry forms (hereinafter, the "Submissions"): 

1\. The Submissions will be shared with our staff and appropriate partners or officials at our discretion.   
2\. The Burchard Group LLC nor Brendon Burchard are obligated to use your Submission or to pay you for any Submission.   
3\. It is possible similar Submissions may be submitted to us by multiple sources and that a Submission may be similar to ideas generated or developed independently by us.   
4\. All Submissions shall become the property of The Burchard Group LLC and will not be subject to any obligation of confidentiality. We  shall not be liable for any use or disclosure to a third party of any of the Submissions.   
5\. The Burchard Group LLC shall exclusively own all known or later existing rights to the Submissions worldwide and shall be entitled to the unrestricted use of the Submissions for any purpose without compensation to the provider of Submissions.   
6\. The Burchard Group LLC reserves the right to delete or change due dates for Submissions, or other specifics, as it deems necessary in its sole discretion. 

** Persons under the age of 18**

We strongly urge all parents to participate in their children's exploration of the Internet and any online services, and to teach their children about protecting their personal information while online. 

The Site is not directed to children under the age of 13. We prohibit registration by children under the age of 13 for all interactive portions of the Sites including chats and message boards. We will not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under 13. 

By registering for our seminars or sweepstakes or live events through the Site, persons under the age of 18 agree that they have the permission of their parent or guardian to register for and attend our seminar or participate in our sweepstakes. We may, at our discretion, require users or registrants under 18 to obtain written consent of a parent or guardian to register for our seminar.

**Protection of collected information**

Protecting your privacy and your information is a top priority. We have taken careful measures to secure both your information and our physical premises. We exercise great care in providing safe transmission of your information from your PC to our servers (unless sent by a means outside of our control, such as e-mail). 

The personal information that you provide in connection with registering yourself for our seminar is classified as Registration Information. Registration Information is protected. Access by you to your Registration Information is available through a password and unique customer ID selected by you. You are responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of your information and password. You shall be responsible for all uses of your registration, whether or not authorized by you. You agree to immediately notify us of any unauthorized use of your registration or password. 

Please note that any information you post to a public bulletin board or chat room, such as the discussion board for staff and interns,  which is only accessible by logging in, is available to all persons accessing that location. 

**Updating information**

You have the right to access and correct your personal information at any time. If you would like to review or edit any personal information we have retained about you as a registrant to our seminar, please send us an email at the above address, call us at the above telephone number, or write to us at the above address. Please include your name, address, and/or e-mail address when you contact us. 

** Unsubscribe**

If at any time you would like to stop receiving information from us, simply follow the instructions at the bottom of our e-mail to you, email [ unsubscribe@lifesgoldenticket.com](mailto:unsubscribe@collegesuccessbootcamp.com), or contact us at the phone number or mail address above.  You should be aware, however, that it is not always possible to immediately or completely remove or modify information in our databases and servers although we will always make reasonable efforts to do so upon your request.  ** Transfer Consent  
** When you submit personal information through the Site, you understand and agree that this information may be transferred across national boundaries and may be stored and processed in any of the countries in which we or our technology services provider operates including, without limitation, the United States. By using our Web Site, participating in any of our services and/or providing us with your information, you consent to this transfer. 

** Privacy complaints**  
We take our users' privacy concerns seriously. If you believe that we have not complied with this Online Privacy Policy with respect to your personal information, you may write us, email us, or call us at the contact information provided above. In your correspondence, please describe in as much detail as possible the ways in which you believe that the Privacy Policy has not been complied with. We will investigate your complaint promptly.

** Your Acceptance of These Terms**   
By using the Site, you signify your acceptance of our Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to these terms will mean that you accept those changes.
